ratemydrawings.com 2010-12-29

# RateMyDrawings - Privacy

> **To help you understand...**
> 
> ###### RateMyDrawings strongly believes in its members’ right to privacy.
> 
> ###### Information Collection and Use
> 
> Your privacy is important to us. We only collect information for internal use to best offer our services.   
>  1) We collect your email address for registration.  
>  2) We use browser cookies to make parts of our website work.  
>  3) Member profiles display any information you enter into them to the public. We save this data for internal uses only.  
> 
> 
> **RateMyDrawings collects three types of information:  
>  **
> 
>   1. RateMyDrawings requires user registration to interact with certain areas of our website. We therefore collect and store the e-mail address you provide in the registration process. 
>   2. We passively record information about the interaction between a web user's browser and our servers. Those interactions include user IP addresses and their interaction with drawings such as user ratings. In addition session ID cookies may be used to confirm whether a user is logged in. A cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer through your web browser that is tied to your login information. The session ID cookie expires once your web browser is closed. This non-identifying information is collected from web users to assist in the proper function of our service. 
>   3. RateMyDrawings allows users to input personal information and preferences in the user profile section of the user’s account. Any information published by users is published at the user’s own risk. RateMyDrawings disclaims any and all liability against claims arising from information published by the user, and we do not guarantee the privacy of that information. RateMyDrawings does not collect, use, sell, or purchase the personal information provided by the user. Furthermore we may also use or share non-identifying aggregate information to better design our web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women registered with RateMyDrawings. However no information will be used that could identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
> 

> 
> The term “Mixart New Media”, “Ratemydrawings.com” “we”, or “us” refers to the owners of the website. The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of our website. 
> 
> ###### Children Under 13
> 
> Child safety is important to us. To keep kids safe and to meet governing standards, under 13's need parental consent to complete registration.
> 
> Parents, as guided by governing standards, we take various steps to obtain your consent. 
> 
> Children under the age of 13 are allowed to register with this web site AFTER we have received verified parental or guardian consent. Information Collection and Use for children under 13 is identical to the one stated above. Identifiable information such as e-mail is used for internal purposes only and will not be shared with any third parties. We advise parents to monitor their children’s use of this website and we request that children under the age of 13 not provide personally identifiable information such as name, address, phone number, age or location on any public area (including your personal profile) of this website. 
> 
> **Parental Consent  
>  **Upon age verification on our registration page, the user will be redirected to the [Parental/Guardian Verification consent form](http://www.ratemydrawings.com/community/register_coppa.php). Parents/Guardians are required to print and fill out the consent form accurately and submit the form via mail, fax, or scan and email a pdf of the completed form to the address provided on the form. After receipt of the consent form, Ratemydrawings.com will send an email notification to the parent/guardian and the child with instructions on how the child may register his/her email address and begin using the website and its features.
> 
> We strongly recommend that people between the ages of 13 and 18 ask parental permission before providing any personal information through this site. 
> 
> ###### Email Address Confidentiality
> 
> Your email address is safe with us.
> 
> RateMyDrawings will not sell or rent your email address to third parties and will only use your email address for registration on our websites and activation of your drawings. We may also notify you via the e-mail you have provided of RateMyDrawings announcements and notices.
> 
> ###### **Information Sharing**
> 
> We take measure and choose hosting and service providers that use the latest secure technology to ensure your information is safe and not shared.
> 
> Web user information such as account and profile information is stored securely at our web hosting providers’ facilities with the highest security implementations offered by the web hosting provider. Thus, we are required to share information only with our service providers so that we may bring you these services. We have taken care in choosing hosting facilities that offer secure measures; however we are not accountable for problems and security breaches that originate with our hosting providers. Account and profile information along with users email addresses are shared only with the web hosting provider and will not be sold or rented to any third parties.
> 
> ###### **Third Party Advertising**
> 
> To keep our site free, we display ads. These ads may track IP address to deliver ads.
> 
> We permit various third-party advertising companies to display ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non- personal information such as your computer IP address to track your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Included in this advertising is advertisements provided by Google or other advertising network providers. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to display ads on RateMyDrawings.  Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to display ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
> 
> ###### **Privacy of information**
> 
> We take measures to ensure our data is safe.
> 
> RateMyDrawings respects its members’ right to privacy. It is our policy not to monitor the contents of accounts or private messages unless such content or private messages are suspected of being in violation of our Terms and Conditions. While we do make every effort to maintain the integrity of account data and private messages, we are not liable for any data that is lost or shared outside of our control.
> 
> ###### **Ownership of Information**
> 
> We own our site data.
> 
> RateMyDrawings is the sole owner of all data collected by RateMyDrawings on the site.   
>  Ownership of drawings is explained in detail in our website Terms and Conditions.  
>  Copyright of content is explained in our Copyright policy.
> 
> ###### **Security**
> 
> We take measures to ensure our data is secure.
> 
> RateMyDrawings takes reasonable precaution to protect the information collected through its websites against loss, misuse or alteration. All information is password protected and only employees of RateMyDrawings that require access to the information to conduct normal business operations are given permission to use it.
> 
> ###### **Web Links**
> 
> Take precaution when clicking links on our site - it is your responsibility.
> 
> When you leave this site through links found on this site to other websites (whether knowingly or not) RateMyDrawings is not responsible in any way for any material that you encounter and RateMyDrawings disclaims (to the fullest extent permitted by law) any liability that may arise with respect to or as a result of such material that may cause any damage, costs, injury or financial loss of any kind. 
> 
> ###### Contacting us about privacy concerns
> 
> At any time you may contact us to:   
>  1) Ask questions pertaining to this privacy policy;   
>  2) Correct or change any information you may have provided through the website; (Please use features available on our website when possible)  
>  3) Remove yourself from our system; or   
>  4) Provide verification of parental consent for users under 13 years of age. To protect your security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your personal information. 
> 
> You may contact us via mail:   
>  RateMyDrawings Privacy Administrator  
>  c/o Mixart New Media, LLC  
>  PO Box 3302  
>  Redmond, WA, 98073
> 
> or Fax: +1(425) 502-6612, or Email: [[Click to reveal]](http://mailhide.recaptcha.net/d?k=01z2_4gSbB2BXHnzhm27hR4Q==&c=EqGyBmJQmlgy7rHLD8-wEwdRHjj8wi_dB0v7wRc6J_4= "Reveal this e-mail address")
